Guide to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association records, circa 1800-2022 MS2027
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Administration files, 1828-2010; MS2027 Series 2
  - Reference files: Georgetown Boathouse -- Vanity Fair, undated; MS2027 Series 2 (Box 85, Folder 26)
  - Reference files: Georgetown Boathouse -- WASA, undated; MS2027 Series 2 (Box 85, Folder 27)
  - C & O Canal Restoration, concept, development plans, 1972-1993; MS2027 Series 2 (Oversize 91, Folder 1)
  - C & O Canal reunions and association file, 1972-1979; MS2027 Series 2 (Oversize 91, Folder 2)
  - Reunion Hike correspondence, flyers, 1965-1979; MS2027 Series 2 (Oversize 91, Folder 3)
  - Level workers, 1970; MS2027 Series 2 (Oversize 91, Folder 4)
  - Williamsport Canal Club, MS2027 Series 2 (Oversize 91, Folder 5)
  - Membership files: Along the Towpath, No 4, 1977; MS2027 Series 2 (Oversize 91, Folder 6)
  - Membership files: Capital Comment by Senator Charles Mathias, 1968-1972; MS2027 Series 2 (Oversize 91, Folder 7)
  - Congressional Records, 1961-1972; MS2027 Series 2 (Oversize 91, Folder 8)
- Audio-visual materials, 1949-1995; MS2027 Series 3
  This series contains film, audio cassettes, videos, and phonographs. These items date from 1949-95. The audio cassettes are recordings of Board meetings, and the oral histories of Lillian Langdon, Louis Cross, and the historical story "My Daddy has a Snow-White Mule." The phonograph is the 1949 recording of "My Daddy had a Snow-White Mule-Stories of the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal."
  - Film, "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal-A Case in American Politics", Part 1, nd, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Film, "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal-A Case in American Politics", Part 2, nd, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Audio Cassette, Board meeting, Part 1, 1994 April 10 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Audio Cassette, Board meeting, Part 2, 1994 April 10 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Audio Cassette, Board meeting, Incomplete, 1994 June 26 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Audio Cassette, Board meeting, Part 1, 1994 August 07 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Audio Cassette, Board meeting, Part 2, 1994 August 07 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Audio Cassette, Board meeting, Part 1, 1994 September 25 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Audio Cassette, Board meeting, Part 2, 1994 September 25 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Audio Cassette, Board meeting, 1995 February 12 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Audio Cassette, Board meeting, 1995 March 04 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Audio Cassette, Interview-Lillian Langdon, 1994 May 26 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Audio Cassette, Interview-Louis Cross, 1998 September 01 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Audio Cassette, Story, "My Daddy had a Snow-White Mule", nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Audio Microfilm, Copies of various Chesapeake & Ohio and other newsletters, 1960-1983 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Video, "The Long Hike-The 1954 Heritage Hike", VHS and U-Matic, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Video, "Years of Construction/Life on the Canal", VHS, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Video, "Joint Chesapeake & Ohio Canal/National Railway Historical Society-Program at Cumberland", VHS, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Video, "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal", VHS, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Phonograph, "My Daddy had a Snow-White Mule -- Stories of the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal", 45 RPM, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Personal papers, 1860-1992; MS2027 Series 4
  This series consists of articles, photographs, correspondence, statements, forms, invitations, maps, reports, and slides. The people whose papers are included are Justice William O. Douglas, C.J.S. [Jack] Durham, Joan Paull, Colin Ritter and William J. Stephenson.
  - Justice William O. Douglas files: Biographical File, nd, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Justice William O. Douglas files: Booklet, "Cumberland to Washington on the Chesapeake & Ohio Towpath-30th Anniversary Hike", 1984 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Justice William O. Douglas files: Correspondence, 1969-1975 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Justice William O. Douglas files: Article, "Towpath Along the Potomac", 1971 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Justice William O. Douglas files: Article, "The Supreme Court Justices-Illustrated Biographies- 1989-1993" (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Justice William O. Douglas files: News clippings, 1954-1980 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Justice William O. Douglas files: Photographs, Justice William O. Douglas, 1955-Circa 1975 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Justice William O. Douglas files: Photographs, First Chesapeake & Ohio Heritage Hike, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Justice William O. Douglas files: Photographs, Reunion hike dinner-Justice Douglas and Cathy Douglas, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Justice William O. Douglas files: Photographs, Reunion hike-Justice Douglas and Cathy Douglas, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Justice William O. Douglas files: Slides, Justice Douglas, nd, undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - C. J. S. Durham files: Biographical File, nd, undated (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - C. J. S. Durham files: Article, "Repel These Invasions", 1957 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - C. J. S. Durham files: Correspondence, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - C. J. S. Durham files: Correspondence, Received from Justice William Douglas, 1958-1969 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - C. J. S. Durham files: Press Releases, Cumberland for Allegany Parkway, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - C. J. S. Durham files: Resolution, George Washington Parkway, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - C. J. S. Durham files: Statement, Sierra Club vs. Rogers C. B. Morton-Mr. Justice Douglas dissenting, nd, undated (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Joan Paull files: Article of Incorporation and By-laws, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Joan Paull files: By-laws, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Joan Paull files: Brochures, Membership applications, nd, undated (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Joan Paull files: Correspondence, Girl Scout visit, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Joan Paull files: Correspondence, Department of Interior, 1983-1990 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Joan Paull files: Correspondence, From Joan, 1983-1985 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Joan Paull files: Correspondence, Volunteer opportunities, 1983-1989 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Joan Paull files: Correspondence, Anne Murphy, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Joan Paull files: Correspondence, Bruce Wood, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Joan Paull files: Correspondence, Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Joan Paull files: Correspondence, Member survey, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Joan Paull files: Correspondence, Mimi Eller, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Joan Paull files: Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1985-1987 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Joan Paull files: Correspondence, Hal Larsen, 1986-1990 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Joan Paull files: Correspondence, Volunteer projects, 1988-1990 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Joan Paull files: Correspondence, Montgomery Co. Community Service Partnership, 1988-1990 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Joan Paull files: Correspondence, Preservation Society of Allegany Co., 1990 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Joan Paull files: Correspondence, David Johnson, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Joan Paull files: Correspondence, Recruitment letter, nd, undated (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Joan Paull files: Flyers, Heritage Hikes, 1975-1983 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Joan Paull files: Flyer, Alexandria aqueduct volunteer project, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Joan Paull files: Flyer, Volunteer opportunities, nd, undated (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Joan Paull files: Forms, Membership renewal notice, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Joan Paull files: Forms, Meeting notices, 1978-1985 (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - Joan Paull files: Forms, Picnic permits, 1988-1990 (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - Joan Paull files: Forms, Heritage Hike dinner reservation, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - Joan Paull files: Forms, Sponsorship registration, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - Joan Paull files: Guidelines, Paw Paw Cabin, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - Joan Paull files: Guidelines, Association telephone, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - Joan Paull files: Invitation, Caroling event, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 48)
  - Joan Paull files: Invitation, Pot luck supper and dance, Circa 1987 (Box 32, Folder 49)
  - Joan Paull files: Invitation, Holiday celebration, Circa 1987 (Box 32, Folder 50)
  - Joan Paull files: Invitation, Christmas Get Together, Circa 1988 (Box 32, Folder 51)
  - Joan Paull files: Invitation, Pot luck supper, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 52)
  - Joan Paull files: Invitation, Holiday Sing-A-Long, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 53)
  - Joan Paull files: Lists, Board of Directors, 1983-1985 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Joan Paull files: Lists, Volunteer projects, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Joan Paull files: Lists, Member directories, 1984-1989 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Joan Paull files: Lists, Officer candidates, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Joan Paull files: Level Walkers, Correspondence, 1982-1992 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Joan Paull files: Level Walkers, Directories, 1976-1979 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Joan Paull files: Level Walkers, Guidelines, 1975-1989 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Joan Paull files: Level Walkers, Forms, 1983-1992 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Joan Paull files: Level Walkers, Lists-Canal section, nd, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Joan Paull files: Level Walkers, Meeting, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Joan Paull files: Level Walkers, Memorandum, nd, undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Joan Paull files: Level Walkers, Report-level 8, Joan Paull, 1975-1982 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Joan Paull files: Level Walkers, Report-level 8, Al Stanley, 1980-1987 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Joan Paull files: Map, Drawing of West Virginia and Maryland in 1863, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Joan Paull files: Map, Shepherdstown to Harpers Ferry, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Joan Paull files: Map, Nolands Island, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Joan Paull files: Map, Hagerstown & Burnside Home, nd, undated (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Joan Paull files: Map, Harpers Ferry-Weverton Heights to Pleasantville, nd, undated (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Joan Paull files: Meeting, Board of Directors, 1976 June 16 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Joan Paull files: Meeting, Board of Directors, 1977 June 18 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Joan Paull files: Meeting, Board of Directors, 1980 April 25 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Joan Paull files: Meeting, Board of Directors, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Joan Paull files: Meeting, Board of Directors, 1982 February 03 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Joan Paull files: Meeting, Board of Directors, 1983 February (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Joan Paull files: Meetings, Board of Directors, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Joan Paull files: Meetings, Board of Directors, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Joan Paull files: Meetings, Board of Directors, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Joan Paull files: Meetings, Board of Directors, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Joan Paull files: Meetings, Board of Directors, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Joan Paull files: Meetings, Membership committee, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Joan Paull files: Meetings, Board of Directors, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Joan Paull files: Meetings, Board of Directors, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Joan Paull files: Meeting, Membership, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Joan Paull files: Memorandum, 1983-1991 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Joan Paull files: Memorandum, Officers, 1989-1990 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Joan Paull files: Memorandum, U.S. Government, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Joan Paull files: Newsletter, Potomac Appalachian, 1988 April (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Joan Paull files: Photographs, Riley's Loch House, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Joan Paull files: Photographs, Canal at Miles 18 & 19, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Joan Paull files: Press Releases, National Park Service, 1989-1992 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Joan Paull files: Reports, Treasurer's, 1981-1990 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Joan Paull files: Reports, Canal Improvement Committee, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Joan Paull files: Reports, Volunteer, 1983-1991 (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Joan Paull files: Reports, Financial, 1984-1986 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - Joan Paull files: Report, Towpath clean-up, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Joan Paull files: Report, Proposal concerning Potomac Co. Locks, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Joan Paull files: Report, Flood repairs, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - Joan Paull files: Report, To Board from president of association, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - Joan Paull files: Report, Summary of Paw Paw cabin-overseer's evaluations, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 49)
  - Joan Paull files: Report, Volunteer project-bicycle survey, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 50)
  - Joan Paull files: Report, Volunteer staff aide project-archives, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 51)
  - Joan Paull files: Report, Flood control policy committee, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 52)
  - Joan Paull files: Report, Internal audit committee, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 53)
  - Joan Paull files: Report, On the proposed Montgomery Co. public safety outdoor firing range, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 54)
  - Joan Paull files: Schedules, 20th Heritage Hike, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 55)
  - Joan Paull files: Schedules, Event calendar, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 56)
  - Joan Paull files: Schedules, Activities calendar, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 57)
  - Joan Paull files: Subject File, 30th Heritage Hike, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 58)
  - Joan Paull files: Subject File, 30th Heritage Hike-Booklet, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 59)
  - Joan Paull files: Subject File, 30th Heritage Hike-Press highlights booklet, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 60)
  - Joan Paull files: Subject File, Paw Paw Tunnel history, nd, undated (Box 33, Folder 61)
  - Colin Ritter files: Article, Potomac Co. Tolls, photocopy, 1860 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Colin Ritter files: Article, "Why not a Canoe-Way?", 1953 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Colin Ritter files: Article, "The Potomac River Valley", Circa 1955 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Colin Ritter files: Article, "Down the Potomac by Canoe", 1960 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Colin Ritter files: Article, "A link with the past", 1967 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Colin Ritter files: Article, "Proposed Potomac National River", 1968 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Colin Ritter files: Article, "Who'll take action to save Potomac?", 1969 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Colin Ritter files: Article, "Mules is born in a man; You ain't gonna get it out of him", Circa 1980 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Colin Ritter files: Booklet, "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal, MD", Circa 1940 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Colin Ritter files: Booklet, "Valley of History", Circa 1960 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Colin Ritter files: Brochure, "The Potomac-Its Water Resources", Circa 1965 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Colin Ritter files: Booklet, "Rockland Co. Conference on Natural Beauty", 1966 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Colin Ritter files: Brochures, "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal", Circa 1969 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Colin Ritter files: Brochures, "The James River & Kanwaha Canal Tidewater Connections Locks", nd, undated (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Colin Ritter files: Correspondence, 1971-1989 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Colin Ritter files: Correspondence, Wm. Douglas-director resignation, 1971 May 03 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Colin Ritter files: Correspondence, Youth Conservation Corps, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Colin Ritter files: Correspondence, Chesapeake & Ohio National Park Exhibit, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Colin Ritter files: Correspondence, Association, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Colin Ritter files: Event, Brad Haigh Memorial, 1995 October 02 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Colin Ritter files: Forms, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal history order forms, Circa 1984 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Colin Ritter files: List, Membership, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Colin Ritter files: Maps, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal, 1960-1967 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Colin Ritter files: Maps, Appalachian Trail, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Colin Ritter files: Memorabilia, Post Cards-Chesapeake & Ohio Canal, nd, undated (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Colin Ritter files: Memorabilia, Sheet music-Chesapeake & Ohio songs, 1955-1968 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Colin Ritter files: Memorabilia, Stamp-National Parks Centennial-First Day Issue, 1972 March 01 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Colin Ritter files: Memorandum, Association, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Colin Ritter files: News clippings, Jefferson Co-Potomac River, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Colin Ritter files: Newsletter, Centennial Observer & Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Chronicle, 1961-1962 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Colin Ritter files: Newsletter, Potomac Basin Reporter, 1975 April (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Colin Ritter files: Notes, "Work along the canal-a history", Circa 1956 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Colin Ritter files: Notes, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal history, nd, undated (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Colin Ritter files: Publication, "The Living Wilderness", 1954 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Colin Ritter files: Publication, "American Forests", 1965 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Colin Ritter files: Publication, "A Guide to Food & Lodging Along the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal", 1994 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Colin Ritter files: Report, "Justice Douglas/Washington Post -- Hiking Trip Along the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal", 1954 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Colin Ritter files: Report, "Potomac Heritage Trail", 1965 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Colin Ritter files: Report, Potomac Interim Report to the President, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Colin Ritter files: Report, "Trails for America-Department of the Interior", 1966 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Colin Ritter files: Report, "Washington Co. Historical Advisory Committee", Circa 1969 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Colin Ritter files: Report, "Interstate Commission of the Potomac River Basin", 1974 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Colin Ritter files: Subject File, Pennsylvania Canals, 1968-1972 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Colin Ritter files: Subject File, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal-National Historical Park, 1968-1975 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Colin Ritter files: Subject File, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal-National Historical Park, Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Colin Ritter files: Subject File, Canal Parkway Development Study, Cumberland, MD, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Colin Ritter files: Subject File, Georgetown University Canal road entrance project, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Colin Ritter files: Subject File, Paw Paw Tunnel, Circa 1966 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Inventories of Slide Collection, Circa 1992 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0001-0010, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 36, Folder 1)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0011-0020, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 36, Folder 2)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0021-0030, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 36, Folder 3)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0031-0040, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 36, Folder 4)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0041-0050, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 36, Folder 5)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0051-0060, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 36, Folder 6)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0061-0070, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 36, Folder 7)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0071-0080, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 36, Folder 8)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0081-0090, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 36, Folder 9)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0091-0100, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 36, Folder 10)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0101-0110, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 36, Folder 11)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0111-0120, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 36, Folder 12)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0121-0130, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 36, Folder 13)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0131-0140, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 36, Folder 14)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0141-0150, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 36, Folder 15)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0151-0160, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 36, Folder 16)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0161-0170, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 36, Folder 17)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0171-0180, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 36, Folder 18)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0181-0190, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 36, Folder 19)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0191-0200, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 36, Folder 20)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0201-0210, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 37, Folder 1)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0211-0220, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 37, Folder 2)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0221-0230, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 37, Folder 3)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0231-0240, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 37, Folder 4)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0241-0250, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 37, Folder 5)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0251-0260, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 37, Folder 6)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0261-0270, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 37, Folder 7)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0271-0280, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 37, Folder 8)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0281-0290, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 37, Folder 9)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0291-0300, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 37, Folder 10)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0301-0310, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 37, Folder 11)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0311-0320, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 37, Folder 12)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0321-0330, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 37, Folder 13)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0331-0340, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 37, Folder 14)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0341-0350, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 37, Folder 15)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0351-0360, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 37, Folder 16)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0361-0370, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 37, Folder 17)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0371-0380, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 37, Folder 18)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0381-0390, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 37, Folder 19)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0391-0400, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 37, Folder 20)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0401-0410, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 38, Folder 1)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0411-0420, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 38, Folder 2)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0421-0430, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 38, Folder 3)